<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<main>

<game name="Get the Skibidi">

<n>0</n>

<name>Get the Skibidi</name>

<ver>1</ver>

<description>

<ru>
Забавная игра "Get the Skibidi" позволит расслабиться и повеселиться людям разного возраста. Набирайте очки, зарабатывайте монеты и обменивайте их на разноцветные унитазы! Ловите бонусы в виде пролетающего Скибиди! Устанавливайте рекорды, набирая очки, и соревнуйтесь с друзьями! Просто наслаждайтесь игрой!
</ru>

<en>
A fun game called "Get the Skibidi" will allow people of all ages to relax and have fun. Collect points, earn coins, and exchange them for colorful toilet bowls! Catch bonuses in the form of a flying Skibidi! Set records by scoring points and compete with your friends! Just enjoy the game!
</en>
</description>

<link>https://yandex.ru/games/app/238659</link>

<ico>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/2977039/2a00000189ab201de0c0d7414887fefa8d63/icon1</ico>

<screenshots>2</screenshots>

<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/2977039/2a000001894522bdcbe60b897abb00224b6a//orig</screenshot>

<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/1892995/2a0000018945235d6d1c8e043244b5e56ec1//orig</screenshot>

</game>

<game name="Among the starlight">

<n>1</n>

<name>Among the starlight</name>

<ver>1</ver>

<description>

<ru>
Among the starlight - эта удивительная космическая игра-платформер, где маленькая звездочка противостоит опасным космическим объектам.
Играть в нее могут люди всех возрастов. Вы столкнетесь со множеством космических ловушек и загадок. Попробуйте поиграть и пройти уникальные уровни!

Особенный интерфейс игры и расслабляющая музыка погружает в атмосферу магического и загадочного космоса.

Удобный игровой процесс позволит наслаждаться игрой, не отвлекаясь ни на что. Скорее начинайте играть!
</ru>

<en>
Among the starlight is an amazing space platformer game where a little star confronts dangerous space objects.
People of all ages can play it. You will encounter a lot of space traps and riddles. Try to play and complete unique levels!

The special interface of the game and relaxing music immerse you in the atmosphere of a magical and mysterious cosmos.

Convenient gameplay will allow you to enjoy the game without being distracted by anything. Start playing soon!
</en>
</description>

<link>https://yandex.ru/games/app/230775</link>

<ico>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/1892995/2a00000188245d0e0af4996b240aba9d3332/icon1</ico>

<screenshots>5</screenshots>

<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/3006389/2a000001889b8357210b18cbc8a9e825c289//orig</screenshot>

<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/2977039/2a000001889b83584b492e29461494749d7f//orig</screenshot>

<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/1892995/2a000001889b83536e6750a95d710de70ed5//orig</screenshot>

<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/3006389/2a000001889b835ccf4fa1589f974c9c0ec5//orig</screenshot>

<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/2977039/2a000001889b835f25aa054b0c83896aed06//orig</screenshot>


</game>

<game name="Infinite Maze">

<n>2</n>


<name>Infinite Maze</name>

<ver>1</ver>

<description>

<ru>
Это популярная игра-лабиринт с бесконечным количеством уровней любого размера на ваш выбор. Играть в нее могут как дети, так и взрослые. Тренируйте ваш ум, играя в Infinite Maze!

Особенности нашей игры :
- это игра-слайдер, просто указывайте путь шарику на развилках
- встроенный генератор уровней
- простой и приятный интерфейс, игра занимает всего ~1,5МБ
- уникальная концепция: размеры лабиринта зависят от размеров вашего экрана
- вы можете настроить любимый размер и играть в него сколько угодно раз
- необычный дизайн лабиринтов в форме мозаики с толстыми стенами
- уникальный путь шарика (показывает текущий путь, возврат и тупики)
- несколько режимов: классический, скрытый, новый "заполнение", генератор размеров
- в игре 2 типа генерации лабиринтов
- система достижений
- магазин скинов с популярными героями: Рик и Морти, Спанч Боб, Амонг ас, Нубик, Скибиди, Хагги Вагги

Форма и максимальный размер лабиринта зависит от размера экрана вашего устройства или окна, если играете на ПК.
</ru>

<en>
Infinite Maze is a popular maze game with endless levels of any size you choose. Both children and adults can play it. Train your mind by playing Infinite Maze!

Features of our game:
- this is a slider game, just point the way for the ball on the forks
- built-in level generator
- simple and nice interface, the game takes only ~1.5MB
- unique concept: the size of the labyrinth depends on the size of your screen
- you can set your favorite size and play it as many times as you like
- unusual design of labyrinths in the form of a mosaic with thick walls
- unique ball path (shows current path, return and dead ends)
- several modes: classic, hidden, new "fill", size generator
- in the game 2 types of labyrinth generation
- achievement system
- Store with popular heroes: Rick and Morty, SpongeBob, Among Us, Noob, Skibidi, Huggy Wuggy

The shape and maximum size of the maze depend on the screen size of your device or window if you are playing on a PC.
</en>
</description>

<link>https://yandex.ru/games/app/183014</link>

<ico>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/3006389/2a00000188736b16cda532b96283e150c91e/icon1</ico>

<screenshots>3</screenshots>

<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/6238841/2a0000018afa15b032d46c33bc2b98352214//orig</screenshot>
<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/1881364/2a0000018afa15b1d59fa377ff954dda3017//orig</screenshot>
<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/1881957/2a0000018afa15b32848f954c87207dc88fb//orig</screenshot>

</game>

<game name="Skibidi Dop Space Shooter">

<name>Skibidi Dop Space Shooter</name>

<n>3</n>


<ver>1</ver>

<description>

<ru>
Skibidi Dop Space Shooter - увлекательная игра-стрелялка с потрясающей графикой. Вы столкнетесь с различными врагами. Собирайте ракеты и взрывайте ими врагов. Бонусы восстановят или добавят вам броню. Попробуйте противостоять целой космической армии в одиночку!
</ru>

<en>
Skibidi Dop Space Shooter is an exciting shooting game with stunning graphics. You will face various enemies. Collect rockets and blow up enemies with them. Bonuses will restore or add armor to you. Try to resist the whole space army alone!
</en>
</description>

<link>https://yandex.ru/games/app/271052</link>

<ico>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/10152950/2a0000018bf1546b27aeda5f44ee011e2b13/icon1</ico>

<screenshots>2</screenshots>
<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/6238841/2a0000018bc8ba053035bac95d701c9970ad//orig</screenshot>
<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/10152950/2a0000018bc8ba06a169464e398355cba512//orig</screenshot>

</game>

<game name="Color Stars puzzle">

<n>4</n>

<name>Color Stars puzzle</name>

<ver>1</ver>

<description>

<ru>
Простая и красочная игра для взрослых и детей. Совмещает в себе 2 игровых жанра: "Три в ряд" и "Крестики-нолики" в трехслойном исполнении, привнося в жанр новое веяние. Попробуйте поиграть и открыть все цвета, слои, а также игровые достижения. Выполняйте сложные комбинации и получайте как можно больше очков. Соревнуйтесь с друзьями и ставьте новые рекорды.

Особенности Color Stars puzzle :

- Легко управлять и интересно играть
- Игровые достижения, фоны и фигуры
- Прокачивайте себя в 3-х слоях игры
- Различные комбинации. Попробуйте собрать комбо из 13 фигур!
- Чем больше очков, тем выше ранг! Давайте поиграем и узнаем какой получите Вы!
</ru>

<en>
A simple and colorful game for adults and children. Combines 2 game genres: "Three in a row" and "Tic-tac-toe" in three layers, bringing a new trend to the genre. Try to play and open all the colors, layers, as well as game achievements. Complete complex combinations and get as many points as possible. Compete with your friends and set new records.

Color Stars puzzle features:

- Easy to manage and fun to play
- Game achievements, backgrounds and shapes
- Upgrade yourself in 3 layers of the game
- Various combinations. Try to collect a combo of 9 figures!
- The more points, the higher the rank! Let's play and see which one you get!
</en>
</description>

<link>https://yandex.ru/games/app/230774</link>

<ico>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/2977039/2a000001885cabaef79f5e3e553364304e68/icon1</ico>

<screenshots>7</screenshots>

<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/1892995/2a0000018866de0db4ccb2c0ecd044080888//orig</screenshot>
<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/1892995/2a0000018866de0c4a7e643b0214e660331d//orig</screenshot>
<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/1890793/2a0000018866de19706c2e137ca3cccb7dca//orig</screenshot>
<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/1890793/2a0000018866de16733f9f696e5276d28b2f//orig</screenshot>
<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/1881371/2a0000018866de1971f7672f5f78a99ef717//orig</screenshot>
<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/3006389/2a0000018866de16f9d4c5e92d8e5bf2208f//orig</screenshot>
<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/3006389/2a0000018866de22f1f6c88fc17ef2874757//orig</screenshot>

</game>

<game name="Skibidi Dop Dop. Head to head">

<n>5</n>


<name>Skibidi Dop Dop. Head to head</name>

<ver>1</ver>

<description>

<ru>
"Skibidi Dop Dop. Head to head" - это игра с физикой в жанре 2048. Соединяй одинаковые головы Скибиди, чтобы появилась новая голова! С помощью физики игра становится интереснее! Головы сливаются и взрываются под песню Скибиди Доп Доп Ес Ес! Попробуй стать лидером в этой интересной игре!
</ru>

<en>
"Skibidi Dop Dop. Head to head" is a physics game in the genre of 2048. Connect the same Skibidi heads to create a new head! With the help of physics, the game becomes more interesting! The heads merge and explode to the song Skibidi Dop Dop Eu Eu! Try to become a leader in this interesting game!
</en>
</description>

<link>https://yandex.ru/games/app/255199</link>

<ico>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/6300668/2a0000018ad09c3445de2945543235c62ff5/icon1</ico>

<screenshots>2</screenshots>

<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/1881364/2a0000018a750f2caa1c069c4f5b30cf9eac//orig</screenshot>
<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/1881364/2a0000018a750f2caa1c069c4f5b30cf9eac//orig</screenshot>

</game>

<game name="Get the Skibidi 2">

<n>6</n>


<name>Get the Skibidi 2</name>

<ver>1</ver>

<description>

<ru>
Это продолжение игры "Get the Skibidi". Здесь новая локация! Новые персонажи! Набирайте очки, зарабатывайте монеты и обменивайте их на разноцветные унитазы! Ловите бонусы в виде пролетающего Скибиди! Устанавливайте рекорды, набирая очки, и соревнуйтесь с друзьями! Ловите бонусы в виде пролетающего Скибиди! Просто наслаждайтесь новой игрой "Get the Skibidi 2"!
</ru>

<en>
This is a continuation of the game "Get the Skibidi". There's a new location here! New characters! Collect points, earn coins and exchange them for colorful toilet bowls! Catch bonuses in the form of a flying Skibidi! Set records by gaining points and compete with your friends! Catch bonuses in the form of a flying Skibidi! Just enjoy the new game "Get the Skibidi 2"!
</en>
</description>

<link>https://yandex.ru/games/app/264402</link>

<ico>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/1881957/2a0000018b6d04cd7e34b1c60d368ea6f5b1/icon1</ico>

<screenshots>3</screenshots>

<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/1881364/2a0000018b3ee8fdedb7379954c968ac34a1//orig</screenshot>
<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/6238841/2a0000018b3ee8ff082465fffa6fbd303e07//orig</screenshot>
<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/1881364/2a0000018b3ee8ffa6c544995845508a9c34//orig</screenshot>

</game>

<game name="Bomberman in maze Mod">

<n>7</n>


<name>Bomberman in maze Mod</name>

<ver>1</ver>

<description>

<ru>
"Bomberman in Maze Mod" - увлекательная игра предоставляет возможность насладиться классическим геймплеем бомбермана, но со своими уникальными особенностями. В игре доступны три режима: классический, где нужно разрушать преграды и сражаться с противниками, классический в лабиринте, где экшн происходит в коварных лабиринтах, а также полноценный лабиринт, где придется преодолеть волны врагов и добраться до выхода. Погрузитесь в этот захватывающий мир и станьте настоящим взрывным мастером!
</ru>

<en>
"Bomberman in Maze Mod" is an exciting game that provides the opportunity to enjoy the classic bomberman gameplay, but with its own unique features. There are three modes available in the game: classic, where you need to destroy barriers and fight with opponents, classic in the labyrinth, where the action takes place in treacherous labyrinths, and a full-fledged labyrinth, where you have to overcome waves of enemies and get to the exit. Immerse yourself in this exciting world and become a real blasting master!
</en>
</description>

<link>https://yandex.ru/games/app/269175</link>

<ico>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/11374519/2a0000018bb3314d7f7a1ab12bf4ae963704/icon1</ico>

<screenshots>3</screenshots>

<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/1881364/2a0000018bb3468276500a1a37ed35c602f7//orig</screenshot>
<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/11374519/2a0000018bb34682fd2873ea943e6643390d//orig</screenshot>
<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/11374519/2a0000018bb34683e395e51107ee73bfb9b1//orig</screenshot>

</game>

<game name="Skibidi Toilet 2048 Physics">

<n>8</n>

<name>Skibidi Toilet 2048 Physics</name>

<ver>1</ver>

<description>

<ru>
Играли в 2048? А если соединить 2048 со Скибиди туалетом и приправить всё это физикой? Получится "Skibidi Toilet 2048 Physics" - уникальная, взрывная и веселая игра. В ней вы потренируете свою смекалку и просто посмеетесь, так как игра наполнена смешными звуками, забавными моментами и драйвом. Соединяйте головы, открывая новых Скибиди, взрывайте их динамитом и наблюдайте, как они реалистично разлетаются в разные стороны. Попробуйте и повеселитесь от души вместе со Скибиди!
</ru>

<en>
Have you played 2048? What if you mix 2048 with a Skibidi toilet and spice it all up with physics? It turns into "Skibidi Toilet 2048 Physics" - a unique, explosive, and fun game. In it, you will exercise your wits and experience lots of laughter, as the game is filled with funny sounds, humorous moments, and excitement. Connect the pieces by unlocking new Skibidi, blow them up with dynamite, and watch them realistically fly apart in different directions. Give it a try and have a blast with Skibidi!
</en>
</description>

<link>https://yandex.ru/games/app/247203</link>

<ico>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/6238841/2a0000018a4aaba440f5fc515c2071ce3e58/icon1</ico>

<screenshots>3</screenshots>

<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/3006389/2a00000189c9d272151615413934ccfdffbd//orig</screenshot>
<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/6300668/2a00000189c9d2796a745eeb037399be2c7f//orig</screenshot>
<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/3006389/2a00000189c9d27bd7fd223c4f5178205bbc//orig</screenshot>

</game>

<game name="Funny Smiley Cubes">

<n>9</n>

<name>Funny Smiley Cubes</name>

<ver>1</ver>

<description>

<ru>
• Игры с цифрами: увлекательная тренировка мозга обеспечена;
• Объединяй кубики, чтобы получать новые кубики с другими числами;
• Нет ограничений по времени в игре на логику и слияние;
• Плавные и простые механики управления кубиками;
• Веселая физика в игре на слияние чисел;
• Объедини кубики и достигни числа 2048.

Но зачем останавливаться на достигнутом? Объединяй числа, набирай очки и из раза в раз бей свой рекорд! Нет никаких ограничений! Продолжай соединять кубики с цифрами в этой головоломке!

Приготовься к приятной графике, удобному интерфейсу, интуитивно понятному управлению игрой на логику и забавной физике!
</ru>

<en>
• Games with numbers: exciting brain training is provided;
• Combine cubes to get new cubes with other numbers;
• There is no time limit in the logic and merge game;
• Smooth and simple dice control mechanics;
• Fun physics in a number fusion game;
• Combine the cubes and reach the number 2048.

But why stop there? Combine the numbers, score points and beat your record from time to time! There are no restrictions! Keep connecting cubes with numbers in this puzzle!

Get ready for nice graphics, user-friendly interface, intuitive control of the logic game and funny physics!
</en>
</description>

<link>https://yandex.ru/games/app/254684</link>

<ico>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/1881957/2a0000018b2d1efae6c1cbb9adbf7d3c9c0c/icon1</ico>

<screenshots>2</screenshots>

<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/6238841/2a0000018b1fff415cf8153d9ddca7c42f50//orig</screenshot>
<screenshot>https://avatars.mds.yandex.net/get-games/6238841/2a0000018b1fff41fedd71d6647a98516ee7//orig</screenshot>

</game>

</main>